Kitchen literally catches fire
Sprays with “butter air” TuN

"A fire alarm lets you know when theres a fire in the house"
Me: THEN WHERE WAS THE FIRE ALARM 2 SECONDS AGO!? TuN

“Oh yeah no that’s smoking oh yeah that’s fire! Oh Jesus that’s fire” 😂🤣 had me dying TuN

How to stop and fire 101: Use canned butter😂 TuN

“Please don’t, make fudge”
“BOY SCOUTS”
“so the whisk is forever gone-“ TuN

"butter, the shape and size of an egg. I'm an overachiever" TuN

“ Why do I feel like this is just gonna explode? “
“ Please don’t.. “
“ Make fudge “ TuN

“People in the 1900s didn’t have hands...”
Flashback to the PowerPuff Girls TuN

Brandon burns his hand, screams "boy scouts" as curse word.... lmfao you slay me! TuN

-sprays fire with canned oil” 
That doesn’t help!! 
I’m wheezing 😂😂 TuN

“Is that a pistachio!?” 
*Says in high pitch voice*
“IT IS!” 😱🥜👀👅 TuN
“Oh this it is butter” 
“In the shape of air”
“Welcome to 2019”
“YEET”
Lmao I am dead 💀 TuN

This guy rlly deserves at LEAST 1M subs ! TuN
I died when you sprayed the fire with can butter😂😂 TuN
Brandon: oh wow butter doesn’t come off
Me: put soap TuN

Di-did you just spray a fire...with canned oil... lmao TuN

Did anyone else yell at him like he would hear us when his back was turned that it was going to overboil? 
No? Just me, ok. TuN

when he turned around and the fudge started rising his reaction is my mood
5:08 TuN

Anyone else find themselves watching this over and over again yet laughing your ass off every single time! 🤣🤣🤣 TuN

“My cup runneth over”
I lost it man
So funny TuN

‘I think hickory nuts died off with the dinosaurs’👏😂😂 TuN